Welcome once again and now
in the next four stocks, one of them is the same OIL which is
also in our team and there was some good
news otherwise we said this is the good news,
Oil India moves very fast yesterday, I do
n't know why it moved yesterday, it is possible that their
experts might have come to know, crude is running
at 65, it has reached 630 but it will
still run because these people have the benefit of crude in it
and Numaligarh
gets some tax benefit
from the North East, so they get the benefit of that too,
keep that in mind now you come to number eight Angel
One, you will remember what IIP they did,
they raised a lot of money from Kapi,
at a price of 2500, how much is the stock running now,
000, it ran on the same day, new investment,
who bought Kapi, see HDFC Mutual
Fund, Motilal Mutual Fund, Goldman Sachs
Name India,
Pru Franklin AB, Sunlife, these are the ones
who bought a lot of money in their different two, two, three
schemes, rest there are
many small names, so  I
think this should be kept in mind and since then there has been a
continuous stock run-up run, so some people
's QIP is running very well, some people
face problems, but keep
in mind Angel One, it has been kept in the green,
Ninth Stock ICC Lombard is
keeping it in the green, quoting Jefferies,
they gave its target yesterday, they have increased it to
50, the logic they gave is that
they have talked, they have interacted with the CEO
and they are
very bullish about the digital issue, they feel
that this company is good for that, well you will remember
yesterday a Yatin had reported that now
all insurance policies will have to be given in digital form
only, there was news that it has become mandatory
and